A Finding Aid to the Polly Thayer (Starr) papers, 1846-2008, bulk 1921-2008, in the Archives of American Art AAA.thaypoll
Archives of American Art
- Organization Files, 1931-2008; Series 7; 1 Linear feet Box 10-11
  - Trustees of Reservations (Box 11)
    - "Polly Thayer had a farm", 2002; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Trustees of Reservations staff and children visiting Weir River Farm wishing Polly Thayer happy birthday.
  - Tuesday Club, 1978-2003 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Tuesday Club Book Lists, 1963-2005 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Williams College, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Assorted Membership Cards, 1940-1953 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Philanthropic Organizations, 1994-2004 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Exhibition Files, 1928-2006; Series 8; 1.9 Linear feet Box 11-13
  This series holds exhibition catalogs, reviews, clippings, notes, letters of congratulations, and other items related to Polly Thayer’s solo exhibitions as well as group shows. Noteworthy exhibitions include "Polly Thayer Starr: Fauna and Some Flora" (1996), which includes a visitor’s book and a notebook, and "A Studio of Her Own: Women Artists in Boston 1870-1940" (2001).
  The exhibitions are arranged chronologically.
  - Catalogue of the 123rd Annual Exhibition of the Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts (1928) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Boston Art Club, "Exhibition of Work of American Women Painters" (1928-1929) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - National Academy of Design Exhibition Group Show (1929) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - National Academy of Design Winter Exhibition Group Show (1929) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, The 125th Annual Exhibition of Paintings and Sculpture (1930) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut Academy of Fine Arts Group Show (1930) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Horticultural Hall, Boston Tercentenary Fine Arts and Crafts Exhibition (1930) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Doll & Richards Gallery, "Exhibition of Paintings and Drawings by Ethel R. Thayer" (1930-1931) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Boston City Club Solo Exhibition (1931) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Jordan Marsh Company Art Gallery, An Exhibition of Paintings by Contemporary Artists of New England (1931) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Ogunquit Art Center, XI Annual Exhibition Paintings and Etchings (1931) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Addison Gallery of American Art Group Show (1931) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Wildenstein Gallery, "Exhibition of Portraits by Ethel Thayer" (1932) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Guild of Boston Artists, "Exhibition of Paintings and Drawings by Ethel R. Thayer" (1932) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - American-Anderson Galleries, "American Portraits by American Artists" (1932) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Boston Art Club, "Women Artists of New England" (1933) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Catalogue of the 128th Annual Exhibition of the Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts (1933) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - National Academy of Design 108th Annual Exhibition (1933) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Catalogue of the 129th Annual Exhibition of the Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts (1934) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - National Association of Women Painters and Sculptors 44th Annual Exhibition (1935) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Catalogue of the 130th Exhibition of the Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts (1935) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Doll & Richards Gallery Solo Exhibition (1935) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Jordan Marsh Company Art Gallery, 6th Annual Exhibition of Paintings (1935) (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Philadelphia Art Alliance Solo Exhibition (1936) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Harrisburg Art Association Solo Exhibition (1936) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Grace Horne Galleries Solo Exhibition (1938) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Institute of Modern Art, Contemporary New England Oil Paintings (1939) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Grace Horne Galleries, Exhibition of Polly Thayer and Susumu Hirota (1940) (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Contemporary Arts, "Tenth Annual Pre-Season Exhibition" (1940) (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Rhode Island School of Design Museum of Art, "Contemporary American Painting" (1940) (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Institute of Modern Art, Paintings by Fifty Oncoming Americans (1941) (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Denver Art Museum, "47th Annual Exhibition" (1941) (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Contemporary Arts, "Polly Thayer: The 1941 Burton Emmett Memorial Exhibition" (1941) (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Catalogue of the 137th Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture (1942) (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Contemporary Arts Group Show, "Favorite Paintings" (1942) (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Contemporary Arts, Mid-Season Retrospection (1942) (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Springfield Museum of Fine Arts Group Show (1942) (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Boston Institute of Modern Art Group Show (1942) (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Springfield Art League 25th Annual Members Exhibition (1943) (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Vose Galleries Solo Exhibition (1950) (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Boston Society of Independent Artists 21st Annual Exhibition (1954) (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Childs Gallery, Paintings by Polly Thayer Starr with Sculpture by Mary Elizabeth Sears (1955) (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Boston Arts Festival Group Show (1955) (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Boston Society of Independent Artists 22nd Annual Exhibition (1956) (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Sessler Gallery, "Exhibition of Paintings by Polly Thayer" (1956) (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Friends Neighborhood Guild, "Quaker Artists of America" (1957) (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, The Lambert Collection: Three Hundred Pictures Purchased in Half a Century (1961) (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Childs Gallery, "Paintings by Polly Thayer Starr" (1963) (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Pietrantonio Gallery, "Paintings and Drawings by Polly Thayer" (1964) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cosmopolitan Club Solo Exhibition of Art from Pietrantonio Gallery (1964) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Norfolk Museum of Arts and Sciences, "American Drawing Annual XXI" (1965) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Chilton Club Solo Exhibition (1965) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Boston Public Library, "The Boston Scene: An Exhibition of Paintings and Drawings by Polly Thayer" (1969) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Boston Museum of Fine Arts, "Special Exhibition of M.F.A. School Centennial" (1977), 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Copley Society of Boston, "A Centennial Exhibition" (1980) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Copley Society of Boston, "Work by Polly Thayer Starr" (1981), 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Alfred J. Walker Fine Art, "Women in Art: An American Tradition, 1880-1986" (1987) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Boston Athenaeum Members' Exhibition (1987) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - St. Botolph Club, "All in the Family: Exhibition of Art by Spouses of Club Members" (1990) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Copley Society of Boston, "A Collection of Little Masters" (1992) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Copley Society of Boston, "Paintings and Works on Paper by Polly Thayer Starr" (1994) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Art Complex Museum, "Living by the Brush: Portraits by Women Artists" (1995), 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Cambridge Friends Meeting House, "An Exhibition of Paintings by Polly Thayer Starr" (1995) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Cambridge Friends Meeting House, "An Exhibition of Paintings by Polly Thayer Starr" (1995) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - The French Library, Effective Light: Contemporary Artists Explore Light (1995) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Copley Society of Boston, "Copley Women Artists 1996" (1996), 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Cambridge Friends Center, "Polly Thayer Starr: Fauna and Some Flora" (1996) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Cambridge Friends Center, "Polly Thayer Starr: Fauna and Some Flora" Visitors Book (1996) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Cambridge Friends Center, "Polly Thayer Starr: Fauna and Some Flora" Notebook (1996) (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Copley Society of Boston, "Polly Thayer Starr: Drawings" (1996), 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Latrelle Brewster, "Insect Pollinators: Sketches and Drawings by Polly Thayer Starr" (1997), 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Brookhaven Solo Exhibition, "Polly Thayer Starr" (1997) (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Vose Galleries, "Mary Bradish Titcomb and Her Contemporaries: The Artists of Fenway Studios" (1998) (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Copley Society of Boston, "3 Masters: Nat Burwash, Kahlil Gibran, Polly Thayer Starr" (1999) (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Copley Society of Boston, "Perspectives in Portraiture" (1999) (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Copley Society of Boston, "Women Artists in the Back Bay" (2000) (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Copley Society of Boston, "Patrons' Choice" (2001), 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Boston Museum of Fine Arts, "A Studio of Her Own: Women Artists in Boston 1870-1940" (2001), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Boston Museum of Fine Arts, "A Studio of Her Own: Women Artists in Boston 1870-1940" (2001), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Vose Galleries, "Poetry of Hand & Spirit: Paintings and Drawings by Polly Thayer (Starr)" (2001) (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Guild of Boston Artists, "A Woman's Perspective: Founding and Early Women Members of the Guild of Boston Artists, 1914-1945" (2001), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Harvard Club of Boston, "Copley Masters Show" (2001) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Vose Contemporary, "Cats & Other Creatures" (2001) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Brookhaven, "'Resident Owned' Art Exhibit" (2001) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - New Britain Museum of American Art, "The Body Revealed: Two Hundred Years of the American Nude" (2002) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Hingham Public Library, "The Work of Polly Thayer Starr" (2002) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Bruce Museum of Arts and Sciences, "The Great American Nude" (2002) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Vose Galleries, "The Work of Polly Thayer Starr" (2002) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - St. Botolph Club and Vose Galleries, "Carved from Darkness, Carved from Light: Works by Polly Thayer Starr" (2003) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Vose Contemporary, "Realism Now: Traditions and Departures, Mentors and Proteges" (2004) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Vose Galleries, "Centennial Exhibition: Polly Thayer (Starr)" (2004), 2004-2005 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Brookhaven, "'Resident Owned' Art Exhibit" (2005) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Boston Center for the Arts, "9th Annual Boston International Fine Art Show" (2005) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Brookhaven, "The Passing Show" (2006) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Vose Galleries, The New England Watercolor Tradition 1920-1950 (2006) (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Art Inventory, circa 1940-1999; Series 9; 4.6 Linear feet Box 13-17
  Art inventory records include 15 disbound binders of art inventory lists that include photographs and descriptions of artwork. The records represent art inventory at Polly Thayer's studio at 198 Beacon Street, Boston. Each page has a photograph of an artwork and its inventory number, along with descriptive information such as the title, dimensions, and medium. There are an additional four disbound binders of photographs of the same works of art.
  There is also one folder of partial inventories of art which were originally scattered throughout the collection.
  All of the art inventory and photographs catalogs were originally compiled and arranged by art consultant Wendy L. Swanton before the collection arrived at the archives. The order created by Wendy L. Swanton was retained.
  The 15 disbound art inventory binders are arranged by inventory number, whereas the 4 photographs catalogs contain the same artwork arranged alphabetically by subject. The original subject headings for the photographs catalogs were retained. Some of the photographs in the photographs catalogs were kept in their plastic sleeves which had stickers that presumably indicate artwork that was sold or given away.
  There is one folder of miscellaneous art inventories at the end of the series. These inventories were originally scattered throughout the collection and are unrelated to the disbound binders compiled by Swanton.
  - Wendy Swanton's Inventory Location Key, circa 1990 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Disbound Book 1 Art Inventory, 1990.1-1990.50 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Disbound Book 1 Art Inventory, 1990.51-1990.100 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Disbound Book 1 Art Inventory, 1990.101-1990.150 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Disbound Book 2 Art Inventory, 1990.151-1990.200 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Disbound Book 2 Art Inventory, 1990.201-1990.250 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Disbound Book 2 Art Inventory, 1990.251-1990.300 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Disbound Book 3 Art Inventory, 1990.301-1990.350 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Disbound Book 3 Art Inventory, 1990.351-1990.400 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Disbound Book 3 Art Inventory, 1990.401-1990.450 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Disbound Book 4 Art Inventory, 1990.451-1990.500 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Disbound Book 4 Art Inventory, 1991.501-1991.550 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Disbound Book 4 Art Inventory, 1991.551-1991.600 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Disbound Book 5 Art Inventory, 1991.601-1991.650 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Disbound Book 5 Art Inventory, 1991.651-1991.700 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Disbound Book 5 Art Inventory, 1991.701-1991.750 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Disbound Book 6 Art Inventory, 1991.751-1991.800 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Disbound Book 6 Art Inventory, 1991.801-1991.850 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Disbound Book 6 Art Inventory, 1991.851-1991.900 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Disbound Book 7 Art Inventory, 1991.901-1991.950 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Disbound Book 7 Art Inventory, 1991.951-1991.1000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Disbound Book 7 Art Inventory, 1991.1001-1991.1050 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Disbound Book 8 Art Inventory, 1991.1051-1992.1100, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Disbound Book 8 Art Inventory, 1992.1101-1992.1150 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Disbound Book 8 Art Inventory, 1992.1151-1992.1200 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Disbound Book 9 Art Inventory, 1992.1201-1992.1250 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Disbound Book 9 Art Inventory, 1992.1251-1992.1300 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Disbound Book 9 Art Inventory, 1992.1301-1992.1350 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Photocopy of Disbound Book 10 Art Inventory, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Disbound Book 10 Art Inventory, 1992.1351-1992.1400 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Disbound Book 10 Art Inventory, 1992.1401-1992.1450 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Disbound Book 10 Art Inventory, 1992.1451-1992.1500 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Disbound Book 11 Art Inventory, 1992.1501-1992.1550 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Disbound Book 11 Art Inventory, 1992.1551-1992.1600 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Disbound Book 11 Art Inventory, 1992.1601-1992.1650 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Disbound Book 12 Art Inventory, 1992.1651-1992.1700 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Disbound Book 12 Art Inventory, 1992.1701-1993.1750, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Disbound Book 12 Art Inventory, 1993.1751-1993.1800 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Disbound Book 13 Art Inventory, 1994.1851-1994.1900 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Disbound Book 13 Art Inventory, 1994.1901-1995.1950, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Disbound Book 14 Art Inventory, 1995.1951-1995.2000 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Disbound Book 14 Art Inventory, 1995.2001-1996.2050, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Disbound Book 14 Art Inventory, 1996.2051-1999.2100, 1996-1999 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Disbound Book 15 Art Inventory, 1999.2101-1999.2150 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Disbound Book 15 Art Inventory, 1999.2151-1999.2186 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume I: Abstract Paintings, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume I: Animals - Cats, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume I: Animals - Cats, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume I: Animals - Cats, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume I: Animals - Cats, 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume I: Animals - Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume I: Animals - Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume I: Animals - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume I: Architecture, 1990-1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume I: Architecture - Boston, 1990-1995 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume II: Figure Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume II: Figure Studies, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume II: Figure Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume II: Figure Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume II: Figure Studies - Children, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume II: Figure Studies - Children, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume III: Flowers, Plants, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume III: Flowers and Plants, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume III: Flowers and Plants, 1991-1996 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume III: Insects, 1990-1996 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume III: Interiors, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume III: Landscapes - Watercolors and Paintings, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume III: Landscapes - Drawings and Sketches, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume III: Landscapes - Boston, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume IV: Portraits of Women - Paintings, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume IV: Portraits of Women - Drawings, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume IV: Portraits of Women - Drawings, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume IV: Portraits of Men, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume IV: Seascape - Paintings, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume IV: Seascape - Drawings, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Disbound Photographs Catalog Volume IV: Still-Life, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Art Inventories, circa 1940-circa 1983 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Printed Material, 1900-2006; Series 10; 1.8 Linear feet Box 17-19, 22
  Printed materials include two scrapbooks compiled by Polly Thayer’s mother, Ethel Randolph Thayer, as well as articles about Thayer, magazines, journals, exhibition catalogs, brochures, exhibition invitations, postcards, clippings, and miscellaneous materials.
  Materials are arranged primarily by format.
  - Scrapbook, 1929-1942 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook, 1929-1963 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Oversized material housed in Box 22, Folder 3.
  - Photocopies of Articles in Scrapbooks, circa 2000 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Articles Including Polly Thayer, 1934-2006 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Original folder title for folder of articles that mention Polly Thayer, but she is not the main subject.
  - Poems and Stories based on Polly Thayer, circa 1940-2000 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Short Biographies and Listings, 1941-2006 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Clippings about Polly Thayer, 1927-2008 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Clippings about Art Fraud Case, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - "Polly Thayer and May Sarton: Portrait of the Artists as Young Women", 1994 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - "Peak Experiences", 1995 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - "Reflections on Life at the Easel", 1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - "A Dean's Daughter Funds Professorship", 1998 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - "Polly and the Bees", 1998 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Articles on Weir River Farm Public Opening, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - "Polly Thayer: Poetry of Hand and Spirit", 2001 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - "Polly Thayer's Century of Art", 2001 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - "Portrait in Determination", 2001 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "Modern Women, Modern Art", 2001 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "Nearly a Century in Art", 2002 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - "A Paragon in Our Midst", 2006 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Polly Thayer Starr Obituaries, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - "Dinah in Hingham", 2007 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Williams and Everett Galleries Auction Catalog, 1900 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Bromfield Art Galleries Exhibition Catalog, 1909 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Italian Language Workbook, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Oversized material housed in Box 22, Folder 4.
  - Town & Country, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    Oversized material housed in Box 22, Folder 5.
  - National Association of Women Painters and Sculptors 45th Annual Exhibition Catalog, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - National Association of Women Painters and Sculptors 46th Annual Exhibition Catalog, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - National Association of Women Painters and Sculptors 47th Annual Exhibition Catalog, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Art Instruction, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries Auction Catalog, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - The Windsor Graduate Bulletin, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Westover Magazine, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Westover Magazine, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Vose ArtNotes: A Guide for Collectors, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - The Voice Newsletters, 2004-2006 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - The Pastel Journal, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - People at Meetings: From the Sketchbooks of Polly Thayer, circa 2005 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Some Poems Learned and Loved by Polly Thayer Starr, circa 2006 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Vose ArtNotes Special Edition, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Brochures, circa 1960-1990 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Brochures, circa 1960-1990 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Exhibition Invitations, 1943-1975 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Exhibition Invitations, 1976-1984 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Exhibition Invitations, 1985-2006 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Undated Exhibition Invitations, circa 1950-circa 1990 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Postcards, 1941-1979 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Postcards, 1980-1989 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Undated Postcards, circa 1970-circa 1980 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Blank Postcards, circa 1960-circa 1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, circa 1940-circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, circa 1940-circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, circa 1940-circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, circa 1940-circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, circa 1940-circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, circa 1940-circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, circa 1940-circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, circa 1940-circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, circa 1940-circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Oversized Scrapbook from Box 17, Folder 17 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Italian Language Workbook from Box 18, Folder 15, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Oversized Town & Country Magazine from Box 18, Folder 16, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Sketchbooks, 1930-circa 1970; Series 11; 0.3 Linear feet Box 19, 23
  There are five sketchbooks of Polly Thayer's drawings. A few of the sketchbooks have annotations or titles on the cover and usually contain a range of subjects such as figure drawings, portraits, and sketches of scenery.
  The sketchbooks are arranged chronologically.
  - Sketchbook of Figure Drawings, Portraits, and Operating Room, 1930-1933 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Oversized material housed in Box 23, Folder 1.
  - Sketchbook, circa 1930-circa 1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Oversized material housed in Box 23, Folder 2.
  - Sketchbook of Portraits and "Sketches from the fights", circa 1933 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Oversized material housed in Box 23, Folder 3.
  - Sketchbook, circa 1960-circa 1970 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Sketchbook from Canal Trip, circa 1965 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Oversized Sketchbook from Box 19, Folder 11, 1930-1933 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Sketchbook from Box 19, Folder 12, circa 1930-circa 1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)